[{"answer": "I think the day was very strong, and Piers, I think you pointed out right the inconsistencies Bernie used that to show that this jury should not believe anything that he says and that at the end of the day Trayvon Martin did nothing to cause his own death.", "docId": "130711pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "How do you feel the day went?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "Well, as I heard, they were attempting to use that with the possibility that there was a lesser part of that involved child abuse that would have in essence given them a third bite at the apple in a situation.", "docId": "130711pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "What was the purpose of that because it got rejected?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "I thought it was a really good opening of the summation.", "docId": "130711pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "Jeffrey, where are we?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "Definitely, and in most states, any reasonable view of the evidence that would support manslaughter would -- it would be given anyhow.", "docId": "130711pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "But do you think that manslaughter is a more likely verdict here given all you've heard?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "I think they've both done a good job but I think the defense has done a superb job and they've had a good no nonsense judge whom I -- kind of like the way I think I was when I was on the bench, you know.", "docId": "130711pmt", "aSentId": 122, "question": "Do you think generally the defense has done a better job than the prosecution from a legal point of view?", "qSentId": 121}, {"answer": "It's so standard.", "docId": "130711pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "Would you be annoyed by Don West and the way he's gone about his business or is that just far from the court?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "Well, it's just -- I mean, it was unfair surprise.", "docId": "130711pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "Going to be trying it up, right?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "No question.", "docId": "130711pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "Now you see, that is all indisputably true, isn't it?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "The crucial part is whether the state can actually disprove beyond a reasonable doubt that George Zimmerman acted in self-defense.", "docId": "130711pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "And from your eyes, Judge Leslie, what is the crucial part of the narrative that could determine whether George Zimmerman is found guilty or not guilty?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "Well, remember, he is a neighborhood patrol officer.", "docId": "130711pmt", "aSentId": 202, "question": "What else is he doing?", "qSentId": 201}, {"answer": "Well, I didn't get to see all of it.", "docId": "130711pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "How did you think when they finished that Bernie de la Rionda did?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "Well, you know, Piers, everybody has tried to tiptoe around about this.", "docId": "130711pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "Invoking Martin Luther King there, a good strategy or not to bring race front and center into this trial when people have been perhaps tactfully trying to avoid that?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "I think that is the choice and what you have to understand, and once again there have been some analysts that don't understand Florida law and even some from Florida don't know it that we have lesser included offenses under Florida law in different categories.", "docId": "130711pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "I mean, do you think there should have been any other options that can be presented to them or is that a satisfactory choice?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "It's not even nonsense.", "docId": "130711pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "It was always going to be on the table?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "Oh, I think this is a formal aspect of a criminal case.", "docId": "130711pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "What do you think the rationale is behind what many view as a very surprising decision by him to say I had nothing to do with this?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "Or to Trevor Dooley (ph) who by the way is a black man who was (inaudible) stand your ground law to defend himself when he shot a white man.", "docId": "130711pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "Why is the balance so skewed towards this case and not to 70 shot in Chicago?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130711pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "What matters is did George Zimmerman think I'm going to die?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130711pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "I mean, we don't actually know, do we?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "Well, to hear the inconsistencies with that story, right, in order for you to believe what George Zimmerman is saying, you have to believe that he did not unholster or reveal that weapon until the moment right before he shot Trayvon.", "docId": "130711pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "Well, this is -- well, here, the...", "docId": "130711pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "...something material and important that George Zimmerman has said?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "I -- I think the prosecution has not made the case for second-degree -- second-degree murder...", "docId": "130711pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "David?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I look at it first a lawyer and the legal issues I think have been articulated pretty well on many of your programs.", "docId": "130711pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "What do you make of this trial?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130711pmt", "aSentId": 574, "question": "I mean, here's -- here's a question I think that, you know, someone just raised to me during the break now, which is that if George Zimmerman hadn't had the gun on him, would he have felt empowered or courageous enough to have got out of his vehicle and to have started walking in the direction of this tall young black teenager?", "qSentId": 573}, {"answer": "Well, it -- it doesn't make a lot of sense to me.", "docId": "130711pmt", "aSentId": 585, "question": "I mean, the thing is a total farce, isn't it?", "qSentId": 584}, {"answer": "You know, the -- the classic learning on this, I think that the prosecution is hoping that they see Trayvon as -- as their child.", "docId": "130711pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "How important do you think will be the fact that the jury is entirely female and five of them are mothers?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "I -- I don't think Mr. Zimmerman is going to be convicted.", "docId": "130711pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "If we -- if we go to the last page of a book you had written about this case, Scott, would you have guilty or not guilty?", "qSentId": 607}]